<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fetcher</title>
    <description>a fresh (so fetch) set of tools  elevating public relations and event management via data science</description>
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Importing Contacts To Fetcher</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Importing contacts from existing platforms can uploaded to fetcher using Commas Separated Files (CSV) or Excel Files. Currently the only three extensions we support are &lt;code&gt;xls&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;xlsx&lt;/code&gt;, and ‘csv’. Before attempting to upload a list of contacts, you need to format the columns correct so that our software understands which fields to populate in the contact table. Currently, the only &lt;strong&gt;require&lt;/strong&gt; fields for contacts are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;primary email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;first name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;last name&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following columns names are currently accepted by GetFetcher.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;first_name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;last_name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;city&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;state&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;primary_email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;full_name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;affiliation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;company&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;first&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;last&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;notes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;title&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;prefix&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;asst_first_name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;asst_email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;asst_phone_number&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;mgr_pbl_name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;mgr_pbl_email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;partner&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;twitter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;instagram&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;secondary_email&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One important thing to notice is we &lt;strong&gt;do not&lt;/strong&gt; accept column names with spaces in them: if you want to upload contacts with secondary email addresses, the column name needs to be *secondary_email**  not &lt;strong&gt;secondary email&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another very important thing to pay attention to is commas when uploading CSV files: CSV files, by definiton, are separated by commas. For GetFetecher.com to successfully upload your file, there needs to be the same number of columns in each row, otherwise that row will be skipped. Therefore, if you have fields with commas in them (such as the affiliation or company fields), you should convert that field to Excel (xls,xlsx) instead of using CSV so we are  able to successfully upload all of your contacts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/importing-contacts-to-fetcher</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/importing-contacts-to-fetcher</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How To Export Contacts From Apple To Fetcher</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are currently using Apple’s Mail application for email, you need to pull your contacts from this application and upload them to GetFetcher.com. Since Apple’s Contacts application does not have a &lt;strong&gt;Export To CSV&lt;/strong&gt; functionality, you can convert the output to CSV in a few short steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, you need to export your current contacts. You can do this by opening up the Contacts application, clicking the contact group you want to export on the left hand panel (if you have multiple email addresses, you will have more than one group).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/export_contacts.png&quot; alt=&quot;x&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, you need to export the contacts as &lt;strong&gt;VCard&lt;/strong&gt;. You can do this by selecting ** File -&amp;gt; Export -&amp;gt; Export vCard ** and then saving the file to your location hard drive. By default, it saves this file in your &lt;strong&gt;Documents&lt;/strong&gt; folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/save_contacts.png&quot; alt=&quot;x&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, you need to use a third-party service to convert your newly downloaded vCard to CSV. To do this, you can go to the following &lt;a href=&quot;http://labs.brotherli.ch/vcfconvert/index.php&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;, and upload the vCard. Make sure you select format to be CSV (not Gamil CSV), separate by commas, and check the box for &lt;strong&gt;Add header line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/upload_contacts.png&quot; alt=&quot;x&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are now finished. You can upload the resulting CSV to GetFetcher.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>/export-contacts-from-apple-to-fetcher</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/export-contacts-from-apple-to-fetcher</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
